# MIKAYLA VOSSELLER



(858) 888-0572 vossellerm@gmail.com

# Business Management, Digital Marketing, & Web Design Customer Experience Driven | Community Builder | Team Leadership

With a passion for helping businesses innovate and grow, as well as complex problem solving, I take a creative approach to applying my abilities and skills in the Digital Marketing, Brand Development, Design, and Web Development arenas with the goal of creating differentiating brand awareness and digital presence. Skilled at HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, React.js, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, and Express.js. I am a highly focused and dedicated strategic thinker that can easily pivot to lead the implementation of ideas and plans.

## Competencies:

- Conceptual & Technical Execution
- Project Leadership & Management
- Organization Skills & Multi-Tasking
- Visual Impressions & Graphic Design
- Social Media Engagement
- Simplifying Complexity

#### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, CA Bachelor of Science: Agribusiness & Minor: Equine Science, June 2021

UC San Diego Extended Studies, San Diego, CA
Coding Bootcamp Certification: Expected Completion June 2022

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## FITNESS INTERNATIONAL, LLC

## Software Developer

LA Fitness is an American gym chain with more than 700 clubs across the United States and Canada.

 Work on different Software Development teams to manage customer facing and internal websites and applications.

EQUIVONT, Remote June 2019 to Present

#### Marketing & Social Media Manager

Equivont is an online resource for equestrians to discover reputable equine service providers and shop quality products. Users can browse horses for sale, equestrian events, and job openings, providing access to the best resources for rider and horse.

- Lead social media campaigns and marketing on platforms including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, LinkedIn, and Mailchimp.
- Manage online presence of Equivont's brand and engage with users, strengthening customer relationships.
- Assist with website design to improve customer experience & engagement, as well as optimize SEO through ad content and weekly blog posts.
- Design and manage websites hosted on Shopify and Squarespace.

WILDFLOWER EQUESTRIAN (Previously Wildflower Farm SD) Encinitas, California, United States

September 2021 to June 2022

June 2022 to Present

Continued, Page 2

## Mikayla Vosseller | (858) 888-0572 | vossellerm@gmail.com | Page 2

#### Bookkeeper - Part Time

Wildflower is a premier equestrian hunter/jumper training facility in Encinitas, CA. offering training and boarding in North County San Diego.

- Manage all aspects of accounting including customer invoicing, accounts payable, accounts receivable, and banking transactions.
- Keep WordPress website, Social Media Accounts, and regular newsletters up to date.

## SARAH POLLOCK SPORTHORSES, Paso Robles, CA

September 2018 - November 2021

Assistant Trainer: May 2021 - November 2021 - Full Time Working Student: September 2018 - April 2020 - Part Time

Sarah Pollock Sporthorses is a premier full-service hunter/jumper training program - for horse & rider - located on the Central Coast in Paso Robles, CA.

- Show experience through 1.20m & International Hunter Derbies on personal horse.
- Schooled horses for clients at home and at horse shows up to 1.10m.
- Taught lessons to clients up to 1.00m with an emphasis on equitation and flatwork fundamentals.
- Managed daily schedule of horses and other riders, horse show entries, record keeping, social media, and website.

## COASTLINE HUNTERS & JUMPERS, Del Mar, CA

August 2015 - April 2021

Assistant Trainer: May 2020 - April 2021 Working Student: August 2015 - August 2017

Top quality training, instruction, management, and care offered to all levels of horses and riders from

beginner to Grand Prix.

## LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

#### **SheCodes Basics**

SheCodes

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

Credential ID: https://www.shecodes.io/certificates/a9d22c17e5870482cdd5949130ab70e5

## **USEF Active Member**

United States Equestrian Federation

Active Since October 2017 Credential ID: 5372234

## **USHJA Active Member**

United States Hunter Jumper Association

Active Since October 2017 Credential ID: 5372234